<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Guide of data.gouv.nc</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/angelinagarae.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Guide of data.gouv.nc</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/angelinagarae.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Presentation of data.gouv.nc</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/angelinagarae.dev/presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:58:39 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/angelinagarae.dev/presentation/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to data.gouv.nc&#xD;#&#xD;data.gouv.nc is the official platform dedicated to the provision of public data in New Caledonia. Its goal is to promote transparency, innovation, and the improvement of public services through access to open data.&#xA;By accessing this data, citizens, businesses, and researchers can reuse this information to create applications, analyze trends, or develop innovative projects.&#xA;Objectives:&#xD;#&#xD;Facilitate access to public data. Encourage digital innovation. Strengthen transparency of public actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Example of projects</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/angelinagarae.dev/reuses/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:55:39 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/angelinagarae.dev/reuses/example/</guid>
      <description>&#xD;5. Reuse&#xD;#&#xD;# Reuse ## Examples of projects Here are some examples of projects that use data from **data.gouv.nc**: - **OpenTransport NC**: a mobile app that uses transport data to provide real-time bus schedules. - **CalédoClimat**: an interactive dashboard that presents climate data for New Caledonia. Have you developed a project using our data? Submit it via the **Reuse** section to share it with the community. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using the API</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/angelinagarae.dev/API/using/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:54:44 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/angelinagarae.dev/API/using/</guid>
      <description>&#xD;API and Integrations&#xD;#&#xD;Using the API&#xD;#&#xD;data.gouv.nc provides APIs to programmatically access datasets. You can use these APIs to integrate data into your applications or automate analysis.&#xA;Example API request&#xD;#&#xD;GET https://data.gouv.nc/api/1/datasets/my-dataset </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add a dataset</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/angelinagarae.dev/productors/add/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:53:44 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/angelinagarae.dev/productors/add/</guid>
      <description>Contributing&#xD;#&#xD;Add a dataset&#xD;#&#xD;Want to share a public dataset? Follow these steps to contribute:&#xA;Go to the Add a dataset section. Fill in the form with the required information: title, description, license, and upload your files. Click Publish to share your data with the community. Make sure your data is well-structured and properly documented before publishing.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
